{
  "data": {
    "title": "231 Quiz",
    "categories": ["Variables", "Arguments", "Functions", "Bonus Question"],
    "questions": [
      {
        "category": "Variables",
        "question": "What variable is constantly visible in the JavaScript code?",
        "a": "Global Variable",
        "b": "Local Variable",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "category": "Variables",
        "question": "What variable is visible only inside the function where it is defined?",
        "a": "Global Variable",
        "b": "Local Variable",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "category": "Variables",
        "question": "Which variable takes priority over another when the names are the same?",
        "a": "Global Variable",
        "b": "Local Variable",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arguments",
        "question": "One can pass an unsigned function as an argument to another function.",
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arguments",
        "question": "How can the type of arguments pass to a function?",
        "a": "typeof operator",
        "b": "getType Function",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arguments",
        "question": "How can the total number of arguments be passed to a function?",
        "a": "Using args.length property",
        "b": "Using arguments.length property",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "category": "Functions",
        "question": "You can assign an anonymous function to a variable?",
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "category": "Functions",
        "question": "What is a valid type of function javaScript supports?",
        "a": "Named function",
        "b": "Anonymous function",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      {
        "category": "Functions",
        "question":"You can pass an anonymous function as an argument to another function",
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "category": "Bonus Question",
        "question": "What is correct about callbacks?",
        "a": "A callback is a plan JavaScript function passed to a method as an argument or option.",
        "b": "Callbacks can be events, called to give the user a chance to react when a certain state is triggered.",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "Neither",
        "answer": "C"
      }
    ]
  }
}
